http://www.roycefunds.com/policies/#sarbanes-oxley-code-of-ethics

Back to Top
Frequent Trading of Fund SharesAs excerpted from the Prospectus:
Large and frequent short-term trades in a Fund’s shares increase the administrative costs associated with processing its shareholder transactions. This kind of trading may also potentially interfere with the efficient management of a Fund’s portfolio and increase the costs associated with trading its portfolio securities. In addition, under certain circumstances frequent trading may dilute the returns earned on shares held by a Fund’s other shareholders.
The Funds’ Board of Trustees has determined that the Funds are not designed to serve as vehicles for frequent trading in response to short-term fluctuations in the securities markets, and has therefore adopted a policy intended to discourage shareholders from trading that could be detrimental to long-term shareholders of the Funds (the “Policy”). The Policy provides that the Funds will monitor shareholder trading activity and will seek to restrict a shareholder’s trading privileges in a Fund if that shareholder is found to have engaged in multiple “Round Trip” transactions. A “Round Trip” is defined as a purchase (including exchanges) into a Fund followed by a sale (including exchanges) of the same or a similar number of shares out of the Fund within 30 days of the purchase. The Funds will make inquiries or take action against any such shareholder whose trading appears inconsistent with the Policy. Purchases and sales of Fund shares made through an automatic investment plan or systematic withdrawal plan are not considered when determining Round Trips.
The Funds may reject any purchase or exchange order by any investor for any reason, including orders the Funds believe are made by short-term investors. In particular, under the Policy the Funds reserve the right to restrict or reject purchases of shares (including exchanges) without prior notice whenever they detect a pattern of excessive trading.
With respect to accounts where shareholder transactions are processed, or records are kept, by third-party intermediaries, the Funds use reasonable efforts to monitor such accounts to detect suspicious trading patterns. Transactions placed through the same financial intermediary or omnibus account may be deemed part of a group for this purpose and therefore be rejected. For any account that is so identified, the Funds will make further inquiries and take any other necessary actions to enforce the Policy against the shareholder(s) trading through this account and, if necessary, the third-party intermediary maintaining this account. However, the Funds may not be able to determine that a specific order, especially an order made through an omnibus, retirement plan or similar account, is short term or excessive and whether it may be disruptive to the Funds. There is no assurance, therefore, that the Funds will reject all such orders. The Funds do not have any arrangements with any investor or financial intermediary to permit frequent purchases and redemptions of their shares. The Funds may accept undertakings from intermediaries to enforce frequent trading policies on behalf of the Funds that provide a substantially similar level of protection against excessive trading.
Although the Funds will monitor shareholder transactions for certain patterns of excessive trading activity, there can be no assurance that all such trading activity can be identified, prevented or terminated.Sarbanes-Oxley Code of EthicsCode of Ethics for Covered Officers of The Royce Funds
March 1, 2016
The Boards of Directors/Trustees of The Royce Fund, Royce Capital Fund, Royce Value Trust, Inc., Royce Micro-Cap Trust, Inc., and Royce Global Value Trust, Inc. (each, a “Fund” and collectively, “The Royce Funds”) have adopted the following Code of Ethics (the “Code”) applicable to its President, Chief Financial Officer and Manager of Fund Accounting (“Covered Officers”) of The Royce Funds to ensure the continuing integrity of financial reporting and transactions. The names of the Covered Officers covered by the Code are listed on Schedule A hereto.
I. Separate Code
This Code is the sole code of ethics adopted by the Funds for purposes of Section 406 of the Sarbanes-Oxley Act of 2002. The Funds’ and Royce & Associates, LP (“R&A”), the investment adviser to The Royce Funds, code of ethics under Rule 17j-1 under the Investment Company Act of 1940 (the “Investment Company Act”) are separate requirements applying to the Covered Officers and others, and are not part of this Code. In addition to this Code, the Investment Company Act, and the Investment Advisers Act of 1940 (the “Advisers Act”) and rules promulgated thereunder contain numerous specific provisions designed to protect the Funds from conflicts of interest and overreaching. Any conduct by Covered Officers required by specific Investment Company Act or Advisers Act provisions or the rules thereunder is presumed to be in compliance with this Code. Each Covered Officer is accountable for his or her adherence to this Code. Any violation of this Code by a Covered Officer may result in disciplinary action, including immediate dismissal.
II. Requirements
All Covered Officers must:
Engage in and promote honest and ethical conduct, including the ethical handling of actual or apparent conflicts of interest between personal and professional relationships;
Act responsibly in producing and produce, full, fair, accurate, timely and understandable disclosure in reports and documents that the Funds file with, or submit to, the Securities and Exchange Commission (the “SEC”) and in other public communications made by each of the Funds;
Comply with applicable governmental laws, rules and regulations;
Promptly report suspected material violations of this Code, including violations of securities laws or other laws, rules and regulations applicable to a Fund, to R&A’s General Counsel and the Fund’s Audit Committee.
Each Covered Officer must act with integrity, including being honest and candid while still maintaining the confidentiality of information where required by law, and place the interests of The Royce Funds before the Covered Officer’s own personal interests.
Each Covered Officer is required to familiarize himself or herself with the disclosure requirements applicable to each of the Funds and must not knowingly misrepresent or fail to disclose, or cause others to misrepresent or fail to disclose, material facts about a Fund to others, including but not limited to officers of and counsel to The Royce Funds, and their respective independent directors, independent auditors and governmental regulators.
III. Avoidance of Conflicts
The overarching principle of this Code is that the personal interests of a Covered Officer should not be placed improperly before the interests of The Royce Funds. As a result, each Covered Officer must: (i) handle any actual or apparent conflict of interest in an ethical manner, (ii) not use his or her personal influence or personal relationships to influence investment decisions or financial reporting by a Fund whereby the Covered Officer would benefit personally (directly or indirectly) to the detriment of the Fund; (iii) not cause a Fund to take action, or fail to take action, for the personal benefit of the Covered Officer rather than the benefit of such Fund; and (iv) not use for his or her personal benefit (directly or indirectly) any material non-public knowledge pertaining to a Fund.
Although typically not presenting an opportunity for improper personal benefit, conflicts arise from, or as a result of, the contractual relationship between The Royce Funds and R&A, of which the Covered Officers are also officers and/or employees. As a result, this Code recognizes that the Covered Officers will, in the normal course of their duties (whether formally for a Fund or for R&A, or for both), be involved in establishing policies and implementing decisions that will have different effects on R&A and the Fund. The participation of the Covered Officers in such activities is inherent in the contractual relationship between each of The Royce Funds and R&A and is consistent with the performance by the Covered Officers of their duties as officers and/or employees of The Royce Funds. Thus, if performed in conformity with the provisions of the Investment Company Act and the Advisers Act, such activities will be deemed to have been handled ethically.
The following conflict of interest situations must be disclosed by a Covered Officer to, and pre-approved in writing by, the General Counsel if material. Examples of these include:
service as a director on the board of any public company;
any ownership interest in, or any consulting or employment relationship with, any of The Royce Funds’ service providers, other than its investment adviser, principal underwriter, administrator or any affiliated person thereof; or
a direct or indirect financial interest in commissions, transaction charges or spreads paid by any Fund for effecting portfolio transactions.
IV. Materiality
In the event a Covered Officer has any doubt as to (i) whether a suspected violation of this Code would be considered material, (ii) whether information relating to a Fund is of a material nature and therefore subject to public disclosure, (iii) whether non-public knowledge pertaining to a Fund is material in nature, or (iv) whether a particular conflict of interest is material, he or she should seek the advice of R&A’s General Counsel.
V. Compliance and Annual Acknowledgment
Each Covered Officer is required: (i) upon receipt of the Code, to sign and submit to R&A’s General Counsel an acknowledgment stating that he or she has received, read and understands the Code; (ii) annually thereafter to submit a statement to R&A’s General Counsel confirming that he or she has received, read and understands the Code and has complied with the requirements of the Code; (iii) not to retaliate against any employee subordinate to the Covered Officer for reports of potential violations that are made in good faith; and (iv) to notify R&A’s General Counsel, as appropriate, if the Covered Officer observes any irregularities or violations of this Code.
VI. Enforcement of the Code
The Royce Funds will adhere to the following procedures when investigating and enforcing this Code: (i) R&A’s General Counsel will take all appropriate action to investigate any potential violations reported to him or her; (ii) if R&A’s General Counsel determines that a violation has occurred, he or she will take all appropriate disciplinary or preventive action and inform the Fund’s Board of Directors/Trustees of his or her decision; (iii) all changes to or waivers of this Code will, to the extent required, be disclosed on Form N-CSR or otherwise as required by SEC rules; and (iv) any waiver sought by the President of The Royce Funds will be considered by The Royce Funds’ Audit Committees prior to approval of the waiver.
VII. Amendments
Except with respect to Schedule A hereto, which may be updated at any time, this Code may be amended only by the Board of Directors/Trustees of each Fund at a meeting of such Board duly called for that purpose.
VIII. Confidentiality
All reports and records prepared or maintained pursuant to this Code will be considered confidential and will be maintained and protected accordingly. Except as otherwise required by law or this Code, such matters shall not be disclosed to anyone other than the appropriate Board and its counsel and R&A and its affiliated persons.
IX. Internal Use
The Code is intended solely for internal use by The Royce Funds and does not constitute the admission, by or on behalf of any Fund, as to any fact, circumstances or legal conclusion.
Date: September 17, 2003, as revised March 1, 2016Privacy PolicyYour Privacy and the Security of Your Personal Information is Very Important to Royce Investment Partners ("Royce")1 and The Royce Funds (the "Funds")
This Privacy and Security Notice (the "Privacy Notice") describes our privacy and data protection practices with respect to your nonpublic personal information that we receive. The provisions of this Privacy Notice apply to your information both while you are a shareholder and after you are no longer invested with the Funds.
The Type of Nonpublic Personal Information We Collect About You
We collect and maintain nonpublic personal information about you in connection with your shareholder account. Such information may include, but is not limited to:
Personal information included on applications or other forms (for example, your name, address, telephone number, and social security, passport, or driver's license number);
Account balances and transactions;
Mutual fund holdings and positions;
Certain additional information obtained in connection with the registration and servicing of your online account (for example, your e-mail address, online account access user ID and password, and security challenge question responses); and
Certain technical information obtained when you visit our website or register your online account (for example, your IP address, operating system, browser type, and cookies) as described below under the heading “Online Privacy Practices” and “IP Address.”
How We Use Nonpublic Personal Information About You
We do not sell any information we obtain about you to anyone. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about you except as may be required to perform transactions or services you have authorized or as permitted or required by law. We may disclose information about you to:
Employees, agents, and affiliates to enable us to conduct ordinary business or comply with obligations to government regulators;
Service providers, including, but not limited to, the Funds' affiliates, who assist the Funds as part of the ordinary course of business (such as printing, mailing services, or processing or servicing your account with us) or otherwise perform services on the Funds' behalf, including companies that may perform marketing services;
The Funds' representatives such as legal counsel, accountants and auditors; and
Fiduciaries or representatives acting on your behalf, such as an IRA custodian or trustee of a grantor trust.
We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you to protect against fraud, or as permitted or required by applicable law, such as in connection with a law enforcement or regulatory request, subpoena, or similar legal process. In the event of a corporate action or in the event one of our service providers change, we may be required to disclose your nonpublic personal information to third parties.
Online Privacy Practices
Our Web site utilizes a variety of technologies (such as cookies and Web beacons) to collect, store, and aggregate data about usage. The use of these technologies helps us analyze and tailor the site for all users and better understand how our site is used, which features or pages are most popular, and browsing and usage patterns. One of the technologies utilized by our Web site is Google Analytics. For information about how Google Analytics collects and processes data, please visit the Google Analytics website.
You also may be able to set your browser to reject cookies. If you do that, the website may be less functional for you.
Whether personally identifiable information is collected during your visit will depend on how the website is accessed. If you are a registered user of our website we will recognize you each time you visit our site if you are visiting from the same computer and browser, even if you do not log in. In this manner, your general usage patterns and other information noted above would be linked to you specifically.
We also offer you the option to sign on using your third-party social network login credentials such as for your Facebook, Twitter, or LinkedIn account. We may collect information generated through interactions with us via social media, such as photographs, opinions, or Twitter handle. Please refer to the terms of use and privacy policies of those social network platforms to better understand your rights and obligations with regard to such content.
The information we collect from and about you may be used internally for our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products and services, enhancing our sites, improving our services, personalizing your experiences, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns. We will never sell your personal information.
IP Address
We may collect information about your computer (including, where available, your IP address, operating system and browser type) for system administration. This is used as statistical data about our visitors' browsing actions and patterns.
Rights That May be Exercised by Persons Located in the EU and California
Individuals located in the EU have several rights which they may exercise concerning their personal data collected by Royce, namely: the right of access to the data; the right to amend and rectify any inaccuracies in the data; the right to erase the data; the right to portability of the data; and the rights to object to and request the restriction of the processing of the data. Individuals located in California have several rights which they may exercise concerning their personal data collected by Royce, namely: the right of access to the data; the right to erase the data; the right to portability of the data; and the right, to the extent applicable, to opt out of the selling of the data to third parties. To request to exercise these rights, please contact Royce at 745 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY 10151, or 800-221-4268.
Protecting Children's Privacy Online
Our Web site is not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13). We do not intentionally collect information on our Web site from those we actually know are under 13, and we request that these individuals do not provide personal information through the site.
Keeping You Informed of Our Privacy and Security Practices
We will notify you annually of our privacy policy as required by federal law. While we reserve the right to modify this policy at any time we will notify you promptly if this privacy policy changes.
The Funds' Security Practices
We maintain appropriate physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to guard your nonpublic personal information. Our internal data security policies restrict access to your nonpublic personal information to authorized employees, who may use your nonpublic personal information for Fund business purposes only. Although we strive to protect your nonpublic personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide or transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
For questions about our policy or for printed copies of this notice, please contact Royce, at 745 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY 10151, or 800-221-4268.
1 Royce Investment Partners is the name under which Royce & Associates, LP, a limited partnership organized under the laws of Delaware, primarily conducts its business.Proxy Voting GuidelinesRoyce & Associates Proxy Voting Guidelines and Procedures
June 5, 2003 as amended through March 1, 2016
These procedures apply to Royce & Associates, LP (“Royce”) and all funds and other client accounts for which it is responsible for voting proxies, including all open and closed-end registered investment companies (“The Royce Funds”), limited partnerships, limited liability companies, separate accounts, other accounts for which it acts as investment adviser and any accounts for which it acts as sub-adviser that have delegated proxy voting authority to Royce. Such authority is determined at the inception of each client account and generally: (i) is specifically authorized in the applicable investment management agreement or other written instrument or (ii) where not specifically authorized, is granted to Royce where general investment discretion is given to it in the applicable investment management agreement. The Boards of Trustees/Directors of The Royce Funds (the “Boards”) have delegated all proxy voting decisions to Royce subject to these policies and procedures. Notwithstanding the above, from time to time the Boards may reserve voting authority for specific securities.
Receipt of Proxy Material
Under the oversight of the Head of Administration, a Trade Processing Assistant designated by him is responsible for monitoring receipt of all proxies and seeking to ensure that proxies are received for all securities for which Royce has proxy voting responsibility. Royce is not responsible for voting proxies it does not receive. The Head of Administration or his designee use Glass Lewis’ ballot reconciliation tool that is directly tied to the daily holdings provided to them by Royce. Proxies are voted electronically and hard copies of any research notes made on the proxy material are stored.
Voting of Proxies
Once proxy material has been received, it is then promptly reviewed by the designated Trade Processing Assistant to evaluate the issues presented. The Head of Administration or his designee, in consultation with a Co-Chief Investment Officer, develops and updates a list of matters Royce treats as “regularly recurring” and is responsible for ensuring that the designated Trade Processing Assistant has an up-to-date list of these matters at all times, including instructions from a Royce Co-Chief Investment Officer on how to vote on those matters on behalf of Royce clients. Examples of “regularly recurring” matters include non-contested elections of directors and noncontested approval of independent auditors. Non-“regularly recurring” matters are brought to the attention of the portfolio manager(s) for the account(s) involved by the designated Administrative Assistant, and, after giving some consideration to advisories from Glass Lewis & Co., an independent third party research firm, the portfolio manager directs that such matters be voted in a way that he or she believes should better protect or enhance the value of the investment. Portfolio Managers may instruct the Head of Administration that they do not want the regularly recurring matters to be voted in accordance with the standing instructions for their accounts and individual voting instructions on all votes, both regularly recurring and non-regularly recurring, will be obtained from such Portfolio Managers.
From time to time, it is possible that one Royce portfolio manager will decide (i) to vote shares held in client accounts he or she manages differently from the vote of another Royce portfolio manager whose client accounts hold the same security or (ii) to abstain from voting on behalf of client accounts he or she manages when another Royce portfolio manager is casting votes on behalf of other Royce client accounts. The designated Trade Processing Assistant reviews all proxy votes collected from Royce’s portfolio managers prior to such votes being cast. If any difference exists among the voting instructions given by Royce’s portfolio managers, as described above, the designated Trade Processing Assistant then presents these proposed votes to the Head of Administration, or his designee, and a Co-Chief Investment Officer. A Co-Chief Investment Officer, after consulting with the relevant portfolio managers, either reconciles the votes or authorizes the casting of differing votes by different portfolio managers. The Head of Administration, or his designee, maintains a log of all votes including when different portfolio managers have cast differing votes, that describes the rationale for allowing such differing votes and contains the initials of both a Co-Chief Investment Officer and Head of Administration, or his designee, allowing such differing votes. The Head of Administration, or his designee, performs a weekly review of all votes cast by Royce to confirm that any conflicting votes were properly handled in accordance with the above-described procedures.
There are many circumstances that might cause Royce to vote against an issuer’s board of directors or “management” proposal. These would include, among others, excessive compensation, unusual management stock options, preferential voting and poison pills. The portfolio managers decide these issues on a case-by-case basis as described above.
A portfolio manager may, on occasion, determine to take no action on a proxy or a specific proxy item and not submit a vote when he or she concludes that the potential benefit of voting is outweighed by the cost, when it is not in the client account’s best interest to vote.
When a client has authorized Royce to vote proxies on its behalf, Royce will generally not accept instructions from the clients regarding how to vote proxies.
If a security is on loan under The Royce Funds’ Securities Lending Program with State Street Bank and Trust Company (“Loaned Securities”), the Head of Administration, or his designee, will recall the Loaned Securities and request that they be delivered within the customary settlement period after the notice, to permit the exercise of their voting rights if the number of shares of the security on loan would have a material effect on The Royce Funds' voting power at the up-coming stockholder meeting. A material effect is defined for this purpose as any case where the Loaned Securities are 1% or more of a class of a company’s outstanding equity securities. A quarterly report detailing any exceptions that occur in recalling Loaned Securities will be given to the Boards.
Custodian banks are authorized to release all proxy ballots held for Royce client account portfolios to Glass Lewis & Co. for voting, utilizing the Viewpoint proxy voting platform. Substantially all portfolio companies utilize Broadridge to collect their proxy votes.
Under the oversight of the Head of Administration, or his designee, the designated Trade Processing Assistant is responsible for voting all proxies in a timely manner. Votes are returned to Broadridge using Viewpoint as ballots are received, generally two weeks before the scheduled meeting date. The issuer can thus see that the shares were voted, but the actual vote cast is not released to the company until 4:00 pm on the day before the meeting. If proxies must be mailed, they go out at least ten business days before the meeting date.
Conflicts of Interest
The designated Trade Processing Assistant reviews reports generated by Royce’s portfolio management system (“Quest PMS”) that set forth by record date, any security held in a Royce client account which is issued by a (i) public company that is, or a known affiliate of which is, a separate account client of Royce (including sub-advisory relationships), (ii) public company, or a known affiliate of a public company, that has invested in a privately-offered pooled vehicle managed by Royce or (iii) public company, or a known affiliate of a public company, by which the spouse of a Royce employee or an immediate family member of a Royce employee living in the household of such employee is employed, for the purpose of identifying any potential proxy votes that could present a conflict of interest for Royce. The Compliance Department develops and updates the list of such public companies or their known affiliates and this list is used by Quest PMS to generate these daily reports. This list also contains information regarding the source of any potential conflict relating to such companies. Potential conflicts identified on the “conflicts reports” are brought to the attention of the Compliance Department by the designated Trade Processing Assistant. An R&A Compliance Officer then reviews them to determine if business or personal relationships exist between Royce, its officers, managers or employees and the company that could present a material conflict of interest. Any such identified material conflicts are voted by Royce in accordance with the recommendation given by an independent third party research firm (Glass Lewis & Co.). The Trade Processing Assistant under the supervision of the Head of Administration, maintains a log of all such conflicts identified, the analysis of the conflict and the vote ultimately cast. Each entry in this log is signed by a Co-Chief Investment Officer before the relevant votes are cast.
Recordkeeping
A record of the issues and how they are voted is stored in the Viewpoint system for 7 years. Copies of all physically executed proxy cards, all proxy statements (with it being permissible to rely on proxy statements filed and available on Edgar) and any other documents created or reviewed that are material to making a decision on how to vote proxies are retained by the Trade Processing Assistant in an easily accessible place for a period of not less than six years from the end of the fiscal year during which the last entry was made on such record, the first two years at Royce’s office. In addition, copies of each written client request for information on how Royce voted proxies on behalf of that client, and a copy of any written response by Royce to any (written or oral) client request for information on how Royce voted proxies on behalf of that client will be maintained by Royce’s Head of Administration and/or Royce’s Director of Alternative Investments, or their designee (depending on who received such request) for a period of not less than six years from the end of the fiscal year during which the last entry was made on such record, the first two years at Royce’s office. Royce’s Compliance Department shall maintain a copy of any proxy voting policies and procedures in effect at any time within the last five years.
Disclosure
Royce's proxy voting procedures will be disclosed to clients upon commencement of a client account. Thereafter, proxy voting records and procedures are generally disclosed to those clients for which Royce has authority to vote proxies as set forth below:
The Royce Funds – proxy voting records are disclosed annually on Form N-PX (with such voting records also available at www.royceinvest.com). Proxy voting procedures are available in the Statement of Additional Information for the open-end funds, in the annual report on Form N-CSR for the closed-end funds and at www.royceinvest.com.
Limited Liability Company and Limited Partnership Accounts – proxy voting records are disclosed to members/partners upon request and proxy voting procedures (along with a summary thereof) are provided to members/partners annually (and are available at www.royceinvest.com).
Separate Accounts – proxy voting records and procedures are disclosed to separate account clients annually.
Proxy Voting RecordSearch by Fund and company name to review our voting record.
Share:
Subscribe:
Sign Up
Follow:
Thanks. To activate, please click the link in the email we just sent.
Close
<1>Close
Please Upgrade Your Browser
You are using an older browser. Some features may not work correctly. Newer browsers are more secure, faster, and more compatible with newer websites. Ultimately we think you will have a better experience.
Upgrade to a modern browser
Download Google Chrome
Download Safari
Download Mozilla Firefox
Download Internet Explorer
Please enter your information
Email
First Name
Last Name
Submit
Sign Out
Thanks. To activate, please click the link in the email we just sent.
Close
User Found. Please Confirm/Update details
Email
First Name
Last Name
Company
State
Choose State
Wyoming
Phone Number (Optional)
Confirm
Close
We've noticed that you have visited our website a few times.Would you like to sign up?
Email
Submit
Thanks. To activate, please click the link in the email we just sent.
Close
Close
We've noticed that you have signed up for our website, but have not validated yourself.Please click below to send a validation email.
Send Email
Thanks. To activate, please click the link in the email we just sent.
Close
Close
To add a Fund please enter your email
Submit
Thanks. To activate, please click the link in the email we just sent.
Close
Close
Interested in learning more?
This content is for Financial Professionals only.
Close
Interested in learning more?
This content is for Financial Professionals only.
Close
Seeing this again?
Check your email and click the link we sent.
(Or fill out the form again.)
Close
Fill out this form to verify that you are a Financial Professional
I hereby certify that I am either:
(i) an associated person of an investment adviser that is either registered with
the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission under the Investment Advisers Act of
1940 or with a state securities commission (or any agency or office performing like
functions);
(ii) an entity with total assets of at least $50 million;
(iii) a FINRA member or registered associated person of such member;
(iv) a bank, savings and loan association, insurance company, or registered investment company;
(v) a governmental entity or subdivision thereof;
(vi) an employee benefit plan or qualified plan that and has at least 100 participants;or
(vii) a person acting solely on behalf of a person or entity referenced in (i) through (vi) above.
(viii) by providing your email and certifying that you are a financial professional, you are opting in to receive information about small-cap investing from Royce & Associates, LP
Email
First Name
Last Name
Company
State
Choose State
Alabama
Alaska
Phone Number (Optional)
Submit
Thanks. To activate, please click the link in the email we just sent.
Close
Thank you for Registering.
Phone Number (Optional)
Submit
Close
Close
Russell 2000 Market Cycles (%)
to
Important Disclsoure Information
Thanks for your feedback!
Rate this article and share your feedback.
Submit
Close
You are currently logged in with the email , would you like to sign out and login with the Royce Funds associated with the
email?
Note: By remaining logged in as current user, you may not have access to the same fund information associated with your email.
Re-Login
Keep Current
